If you build for the web you've hit this problem before: your app runs on localhost, but the
thing that needs to reach it, a webhook, a client, your phone, is out on the internet
and localhost isn't.
You need a simple way to share what you're building with someone else, and you
can easily do that with viaduct.
I have a local app here, just running on this machine, in fact on
port 8080. It's a little web app, and I want to share it with a friend. To
do that I can ask viaduct to map port 8080 and give me a friendly URL I can share.
It's given me calm-narwhal.viaduct.sh, and this maps directly to the application running
on my machine.
I can share this with anyone on the internet and they can see the same application.
It's a nice, friendly way to quickly share what you're building.
viaduct also comes with lots of different features.
You can turn on the live traffic inspector to see what the app is doing, and interact
with it in real time and see what's going on, all from your terminal.
It's nice and simple, and free to use.
There's no sign-up required.
I built viaduct because I wanted a tunnel small enough to trust.
It's completely open source, a few thousand lines of Python, easy to read, and the
whole thing can be run on your own box.
I'm Adam, and that's viaduct.